<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string-array name="PBJ_list">
        <item>PB+J Muffins</item>
        <item>PB+J Smoothie</item>
        <item>PB+J Donuts</item>
        <item>PB+J Overnight Oats</item>
        <item>PB+J Granola</item>
        <item>PB+J Sandwich</item>
        <item>PB+J Cups</item>
        <item>PB+J Waffle-Grilled Sandwich</item>
        <item>PB+J Ice Cream Sandwiches</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="PBJMuffinsIngredients">Flour\nSalt\nBaking Powder\nMilk\nSugar\nPeanut Butter\nVegetable Oil\nJam</string>
    <string name="PBJMuffinsInstructions">HEAT oven to 375ºF. Spray muffin pan with no-stick cooking spray. Stir together flour, salt and baking powder in a large bowl. Add milk, eggs, 2/3 cup sugar, peanut butter and oil to bowl. Combine ingredients on low speed of electric mixer, just until moistened. Do not over beat.\n\nFILL prepared muffin cups evenly with half of the batter. Place 2 level teaspoons jam or preserves in the center of each muffin. Evenly divide remaining batter between muffin cups. Sprinkle with 1/4 cup sugar. Bake 18 to 20 minutes. Remove from oven. Cool in pan 5 minutes.</string>
    <string name="PBJMuffinsURL">0wa6oaErm7c</string>

    <string name="PBJSmoothieIngredients">Strawberries\nFrozen Banana\nPeanut Butter\nYogurt or Fat Free Milk\nIce Cubes</string>
    <string name="PBJSmoothieInstructions">Place all the ingredients in a blender, and mix until smooth. Enjoy immediately.</string>
    <string name="PBJSmoothieURL">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fGYvPe7Ssp0</string>

    <string name="PBJDonutsIngredients">Milk\nYeast\nSugar\nButter\nEgg\nSalt\nFlour\nCanola Oil\nGrape Jelly\nIcing Sugar\nPeanut Butter\nWater</string>
    <string name="PBJDonutsInstructions">MICROWAVE milk until warm, 45 sec. Pour into bowl of a stand mixer fitted with dough hook. Add yeast and stir. Let stand for 10 min.\n\nBEAT in granulated sugar, butter, egg and salt. Add flour. Beat on medium-high until dough forms a ball and pulls away cleanly from the sides and bottom of the bowl, about 5 min. (Mixer may move around the counter during beating process.)\n\nSPRAY a medium bowl with oil. Line a large baking sheet with parchment. Lightly spray with oil.\n\nSCRAPE dough out of mixer bowl into oiled bowl. Lightly oil top of dough and cover with a damp tea towel (not terry cloth). Let stand in a warm place until dough doubles in size, about 1 hour.\n\nROLL out dough on a floured surface to 1/2 to 3/4 in. thick. Using a 3-in. round cutter, cut into 12 rounds. Transfer to prepared sheet. Cover with same damp tea towel and let stand until doughnuts double in size, about 45 min.\n\nPOUR oil into a pot until it reaches 1 in. up the sides. Clip a deep-fry thermometer to the side. Heat over medium until temperature reaches 325F. Adjust heat as necessary to keep temperature at 325F during cooking. Fry doughnuts, 4 at a time, flipping halfway through, until golden, 3 to 4 min. Drain on paper towels.\n\nPOKE a hole into the side of each doughnut with a medium round piping tip. Attach tip to a piping bag and fill bag with grape jelly. Pipe jelly into holes.\n\nWHISK icing sugar with peanut butter and water in a small bowl until smooth. Spread glaze over tops of doughnuts.</string>
    <string name="PBJDonutsURL">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FtYFS24CcyY</string>

    <string name="PBJOvernightOatsIngredients">Banana\nAlmond Milk\nPeanut Butter\nRolled Oats\nGrape Juice</string>
    <string name="PBJOvernightOatsInstructions">In a stand mixer or using a bowl and hand mixer, whip the banana, almond milk, peanut butter and a pinch of salt until smooth and creamy. Add in the oats and whip until combined.\n\nMove into a container and place in the fridge overnight.\n\nWhisk the chia seeds into the concord grape juice and set into the fridge.\n\nIn the morning, place divide the peanut butter mixture into jars (will make two large servings, 4 smaller ones. Will also keep for at least 2-3 days in the fridge so you can have multiple servings from one recipe).\n\nTop with grape chia mixture.</string>
    <string name="PBJOvernightOatsURL">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MQHqekDSAuc</string>

    <string name="PBJGranolaIngredients">Oats\nPeanuts\nPecans\nWheat Germ\nSalt\nGinger\nCinnamon\nBrown Sugar\nHoney\nPeanut Butter\nReal Vanilla Extract\nOlive Oil\nRaisins\nCranberries</string>
    <string name="PBJGranolaInstructions">Preheat your oven to 325 degrees and line your sheet pan with a silpat or parchment paper.\n\nIn a large bowl combine the nuts, oats, wheat germ, cinnamon, ground ginger and kosher salt. Stir to combine.\n\nIn a small sauce pan, stir the honey and dark brown sugar. Heat over medium, stirring often until bubbling. Remove and turn off the heat. Carefully add in the peanut butter and vanilla, stir. Pour the peanut butter mixture over the nuts and stir until mixed thoroughly. Pour in the olive oil and stir until all of the oil is mixed in.\n\nPour the mixture onto the prepared pan and spread it out evenly. Slide it into the preheated oven and bake for 35-40 minutes stirring twice at every 15 minute mark. Remove and mix in the raisins and dried cranberries.\n\nLet cool before storing in an airtight container.</string>
    <string name="PBJGranolaURL">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=woBFTudr-P0</string>

    <string name="PBJSandwichIngredients">Butter\nWhite Bread\nPeanut Butter\nJelly</string>
    <string name="PBJSandwichInstructions">Heat griddle or skillet to 350 degrees F (175 degrees C).\n\nSpread butter on one side of each slice of bread. Spread peanut butter on unbuttered side of one slice of bread, and jelly on the other. Place one slice, buttered side down on the griddle. Top with other slice, so that peanut butter and jelly are in the middle. Cook for 4 minutes on each side, or until golden brown, and heated through.</string>
    <string name="PBJSandwichURL">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YW7gkczp8ao</string>

    <string name="PBJCupsIngredients">Chocolate Chips\nCoconut Oil\nPeanut Butter\nJelly</string>
    <string name="PBJCupsInstructions">Prepare 24 mini cupcake liners on a baking sheet sized to fit your freezer. Note: You will need a total of 2 hrs of chill time for this recipe\n\nFor melting chocolate: set a sauce pan over medium heat containing about an inch of water, then place a glass, or heat proof bowl over the sauce pan. Careful not to let the simmering water touch the bowl. Add chocolate chips and coconut oil, stir to combine. When completely melted, carefully remove from saucepan and set aside to cool for a minute.\n\nUsing a ½ tablespoon measuring spoon, pour measured melted chocolate into each mini cupcake liner. When done transfer to the freezer. Freeze for about an hour, until hardened. Set remaining melted chocolate aside for later.\n\nMeanwhile, scoop peanut butter into a sandwich sized ziploc bag and cut a ¼ inch hole off one corner (make sure it’s not dripping in oil, if so add 2 tablespoons of powdered sugar as Love and Lemons does. My peanut butter is a no-stir type and relatively “oil free” with only peanuts and salt as the ingredients).\n\nScoop jelly into another sandwich bag and do the same. When bottom layer has hardened, pipe about ½ of a teaspoons worth of peanut butter in the center of each cup. Then freeze all the cups for 15 minutes and repeat with jelly. I did more like a heaping ½ teaspoon of jelly.\n\nPour another ½-1 tablespoon of the remaining melted chocolate (we are not using tempered chocolate here since we all plan to eat these in a matter of minutes! hehe) to cover fully. Make sure to fill any open areas along the cupcake liners.\n\nFreeze another 30 minutes to an hour until hardened. Thaw at room temperature or refrigerate for 20-30 minutes before eating to allow the peanut butter to soften up.</string>
    <string name="PBJCupsURL">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=F4OCxceWPrE</string>

    <string name="PBJWaffleGrilledSandwichIngredients">Biscuits\nPeanut Butter\nJelly\nSugar\nFruit</string>
    <string name="PBJWaffleGrilledSandwichInstructions">Heat Belgian or regular waffle maker according to manufacturers directions. Separate dough into 8 biscuits; press or roll each into 4-inch round.\n\nDepending on size of waffle maker, place 2 to 4 biscuit rounds at a time in hot waffle maker. Bake 2 minutes or until golden brown. Cool 1 to 2 minutes.\n\nSpread peanut butter evenly on 4 of the hot waffles; spread jelly on remaining 4 waffles. Place jelly-spread waffles, jelly down, on peanut butter-spread waffles. Cut sandwiches in half; place on individual plates. Sprinkle with powdered sugar; garnish with fruit.</string>
    <string name="PBJWaffleGrilledSandwichURL">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zaIaa8Wy77c</string>

    <string name="PBJIceCreamSandwichesIngredients">Ice Cream\nPeanut Butter\nGraham Crackers\nJelly</string>
    <string name="PBJIceCreamSandwichesInstructions">Spoon the ice cream into the mixing bowl. Soften it by leaving the ice cream out on the counter for 10 minutes.\n\nMix the peanut butter into the ice cream with the rubber spatula.\n\nLine the baking dish with waxed paper and spread the peanut butter- ice cream mixture on the waxed paper. Cover the mixture with another sheet of waxed paper, and then put the mixture in the freezer for 20 to 45 minutes, or until solid.\n\nTurn the frozen mixture out onto the cutting board, and peel off the waxed paper. Use the chef’s knife to cut the mixture into nine squares the same size as the graham crackers you’re using.\n\nWith the table knife, spread the jam or jelly on a graham cracker, add a square of peanut butter-ice cream mixture, and top with another graham cracker. Put each finished sandwich in the freezer immediately, so it doesn’t melt before you’ve made them all. You can also wrap each PB+J Ice Cream Sandwich in plastic wrap and store them in a freezer bag in the freezer.</string>
    <string name="PBJIceCreamSandwichesURL">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=c7iA5m80mx8</string>
</resources>